# Joel Jang

Last updated on Feb 11, 2023

### joeljang.github.io ♦ joeljang@kaist.ac.kr

### RESEARCH INTERESTS

My main research goal is to build large neural models that are applicable to real-world scenarios, by addressing inherent limitations of current neural models. Specifically, I am interested in allowing neural models to be lifelong learners [C1, C2, P1], providing privacy and security guarantees for neural models [P2], and enabling neural models to follow the given instruction via prompt [W1, C3, P3, P4].

### **EDUCATION**

### M.S. in Artificial Intelligence

Seoul, Korea

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

03/2021 - 08/2023

Graduate School of AI | Language & Knowledge Lab

Advisor: Minjoon Seo

## **B.S.** in Computer Science and Engineering

Seoul, Korea

Korea University

03/2017 - 02/2021

### **PUBLICATIONS**

# **Conference Papers**

[C3] Guess the Instruction! Making Language Models Stronger Zero-shot Learners Seonghyeon Ye, Doyoung Kim, **Joel Jang**, Joongbo Shin, Minjoon Seo ICLR 2023 [paper][code]

[C2] TemporalWiki: A Lifelong Benchmark for Training and Evaluating Ever-Evolving Language Models **Joel Jang\***, Seonghyeon Ye\*, Changho Lee, Sohee Yang, Joongbo Shin, Janghoon Han, Gyeonghun Kim, Minjoon Seo

EMNLP 2022 [paper][code]

[C1] Towards Continual Knowledge Learning of Language Models **Joel Jang**, Seonghyeon Ye, Sohee Yang, Joongbo Shin, Janghoon Han, Gyeonghun Kim, Stanley Jungkyu Choi, Minjoon Seo ICLR 2022 [paper] [code]

### **Workshop Papers**

[W1] Can Large Language Models Truly Follow Your Instructions? Case-study with Negated Prompts **Joel Jang\***, Seonghyeon Ye\*, Minjoon Seo NeurIPS 2022 Workshop on Transfer Learning for NLP (TL4NLP) [paper][code]

# **Journal Papers**

[J2] Sequential Targeting: A Continual Learning Approach for Data Imbalance in Text Classification **Joel Jang**, Yoonjeon Kim, Kyoungho Choi, Sungho Suh Expert Systems With Applications (2021) [paper] [code]

[J1] Supervised Health Stage Prediction Using Convolution Neural Networks for Bearing Wear Sungho Suh, **Joel Jang**, Seungjae Won, Mayank S. Jha, Yong Oh Lee Sensors (2020) [paper] [code]

# **Preprints**

[P4] Gradient Ascent Post-training Enhances Language Model Generalization Dongkeun Yoon\*, Joel Jang\*, Sungdong Kim, Minjoon Seo Submitted to ACL 2023

[P3] Retrieval of Soft Prompt Enhances Zero-shot Task Generalization Seonghyeon Ye, Joel Jang, Doyoung Kim, Yongrae Jo, Minjoon Seo Submitted to ACL 2023 [paper][code]

[P2] Knowledge Unlearning for Mitigating Privacy Risks in Language Models Joel Jang, Dongkeun Yoon, Sohee Yang, Sungmin Cha, Moontae Lee, Lajanugen Logeswaran, Minjoon Seo Submitted to ACL 2023 [paper][code]

[P1] Fixed Input Parameterization for Efficient Prompting Eunbi Choi, Yongrae Jo, Joel Jang, Minjoon Seo Submitted to ACL 2023, [paper][code]

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Allen Institute of AI (AI2) | Mosaic Team

Seattle, US

Research Intern 06/2023-

To Be Decided

LG AI Research Seoul, Korea

Research Intern (Mentors: Moontae Lee, Lajanugen Logeswaran)

07/2022-Current

Working on (1) knowledge unlearning for LMs & (2) unseen task generalization with expert LMs

Kakao Brain Seongnam, Korea

Research Intern (Mentor: Ildoo Kim)

12/2020-02/2021

Worked on large-scale representation learning with weak supervision of images and caption data using TPUs

**NAVER** Seongnam, Korea

Software Engineer Intern

07/2020-09/2020

Worked on hate speech detection model, AI Clean Bot 2.0 (40+ million monthly users, >80% of Korean population) Developed novel method of handling data imbalance using continual learning (paper published under ESWA)

**KIST Europe** Saarbrucken, Germany

Research Intern (Mentor: Yong Oh Lee)

08/2019-01/2020

Worked on anomaly detection & remaining useful life prediction of machinery (paper published under Sensors) Gave an Oral Presentation at PHM Korea 2020 (2020. 07. 23)

### **SERVICES**

#### **Conference Reviewer**

COLING 2022, EMNLP 2022, AKBC 2022, ICLR 2023, ACL 2023

### Journal Reviewer

Journal of Artificial Intelligence Research (JAIR)

### **TEACHING**

12.1011.70	
(KAIST AI599) AI for Law	09/2022-Current
Teaching Assistant (TA)	
(KAIST AI605) Deep Learning for NLP	03/2022-06/2022
Teaching Assistant (TA)	
INVITED TALKS	
Expert Language Models	02/2023
UNC at Chapel Hill (Host: Colin Raffel)	
Temporal Adaptation of Language Models	08/2022
Korean AI Association Summer NLP Session (Host: Minjoon Seo)	
Temporal Adaptation of Language Models	07/2022
KAIST School of Computing (Host: Alice Oh)	
Temporal Adaptation of Language Models	05/2022
Hyperconnect (Host: Buru Chang)	

### **HONORS AND AWARDS**

Qualcomm Innovation Fellowship Korea (QIFK) 2022

Grand Prize in Graduation Capstone Competition (Best Paper Award), 2020 (Advisor: Jaewoo Kang)

4th place, AI NLP Challenge Enliple Cup, 2020

3<sup>rd</sup> place, HAAFOR Challenge 2019

Future Global Leader Scholarships, Korea University, 2019

Best Innovation Award, Intel AI Drone Hackathon, 2018

### LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

Bilingual in English (2004-2016 in US) and Korean (native)

GRE: 326 (Verbal, 157/170, 76th Percentile) | Quant, 169/170, 95th Percentile | Writing, 5.0/6.0, 92nd Percentile)

TOEFL: 119/120 (Reading, 30 | Listening, 30 | Speaking, 29 | Writing, 30)

SAT: 1530/1600 (Reading and Writing, 730 | Math, 800)